[ 
{ "question": "What is 23 + 12?", "answers": ["35", "38", "55", "28"], "correct": "35" },
{ "question": "BONUS:What is 9 * 5?", "answers": ["18", "92", "45", "40"], "correct": "45","isBonus": true },
{ "question": "BONUS:What is 24 / 3?", "answers": ["8", "15", "62", "72"], "correct": "8" ,"isBonus": true},
{ "question": "BONUS:What is 5 * 7?", "answers": ["21", "35", "73", "61"], "correct": "35","isBonus": true },
{ "question": "BONUS:What is 27 / 3?", "answers": ["30", "44", "9", "21"], "correct": "9" ,"isBonus": true},
{ "question": "BONUS:What is 98 + 69?", "answers": ["167", "54", "87", "42"], "correct": "167","isBonus": true },
{ "question": "BONUS:What is 14 + 85?", "answers": ["91", "46", "99", "79"], "correct": "99" ,"isBonus": true},
{ "question": "BONUS:What is 35 / 5?", "answers": ["7", "12", "19", "81"], "correct": "7" ,"isBonus": true},
{ "question": "BONUS:What is 8 * 5?", "answers": ["40", "27", "60", "100"], "correct": "40" ,"isBonus": true},
{ "question": "BONUS:What is 20 - 32?", "answers": ["-34", "-12", "-16", "46"], "correct": "-12" ,"isBonus": true},
{ "question": "BONUS:What is 9 * 9?", "answers": ["89", "83", "81", "27"], "correct": "81" ,"isBonus": true},
{ "question": "BONUS:What is 77 + 44?", "answers": ["97", "98", "121", "52"], "correct": "121" ,"isBonus": true},
{ "question": "What is 58 - 78?", "answers": ["58", "-20", "48", "33"], "correct": "-20" },
{ "question": "What is 9 * 6?", "answers": ["54", "77", "59", "35"], "correct": "54" },
{ "question": "What is 84 - 76?", "answers": ["50", "52", "73", "8"], "correct": "8" },
{ "question": "What is 35 / 7?", "answers": ["27", "43", "96", "5"], "correct": "5" },
{ "question": "What is 55 - 78?", "answers": ["73", "-21", "43", "-23"], "correct": "-23" },
{ "question": "What is 54 - 50?", "answers": ["78", "47", "4", "51"], "correct": "4" },
{ "question": "What is 25 / 5?", "answers": ["48", "5", "65", "75"], "correct": "5" },
{ "question": "What is 87 + 86?", "answers": ["173", "72", "155", "149"], "correct": "173" },
{ "question": "What is 42 + 93?", "answers": ["52", "14", "71", "135"], "correct": "135" },
{ "question": "What is 8 * 7?", "answers": ["47", "19", "56", "47"], "correct": "56" },
{ "question": "What is 18 / 3?", "answers": ["96", "6", "34", "94"], "correct": "6" },
{ "question": "What is 31 - 25?", "answers": ["99", "6", "35", "17"], "correct": "6" },
{ "question": "What is 8 * 5?", "answers": ["72", "42", "70", "40"], "correct": "40" },
{ "question": "What is 28 / 4?", "answers": ["13", "78", "62", "7"], "correct": "7" },
{ "question": "What is 19 - 95?", "answers": ["51", "-61", "-76", "15"], "correct": "-76" },
{ "question": "What is 22 - 79?", "answers": ["39", "-57", "97", "27"], "correct": "-57" },
{ "question": "What is 8 * 6?", "answers": ["13", "20", "48", "13"], "correct": "48" },
{ "question": "What is 33 + 48?", "answers": ["38", "81", "55", "33"], "correct": "81" },
{ "question": "What is 24 + 79?", "answers": ["89", "97", "17", "103"], "correct": "103" },
{ "question": "What is 32 - 72?", "answers": ["97", "-66", "-25", "-40"], "correct": "-40" },
{ "question": "What is 52 - 64?", "answers": ["74", "-12", "-46", "74"], "correct": "-12" },
{ "question": "What is 72 / 8?", "answers": ["82", "9", "43", "35"], "correct": "9" },
{ "question": "What is 22 - 95?", "answers": ["-82", "-46", "15", "-73"], "correct": "-73" },
{ "question": "What is 24 / 3?", "answers": ["31", "14", "8", "32"], "correct": "8" },
{ "question": "What is 24 / 4?", "answers": ["72", "17", "6", "71"], "correct": "6" },
{ "question": "What is 94 + 50?", "answers": ["83", "144", "65", "40"], "correct": "144" },
{ "question": "What is 19 - 54?", "answers": ["-35", "67", "-35", "-60"], "correct": "-35" },
{ "question": "What is 86 - 46?", "answers": ["70", "70", "40", "34"], "correct": "40" },
{ "question": "What is 24 - 85?", "answers": ["56", "-61", "87", "44"], "correct": "-61" },
{ "question": "What is 35 / 7?", "answers": ["27", "5", "94", "94"], "correct": "5" },
{ "question": "What is 72 / 8?", "answers": ["86", "65", "80", "9"], "correct": "9" },
{ "question": "What is 34 + 81?", "answers": ["115", "50", "20", "97"], "correct": "115" },
{ "question": "What is 40 - 70?", "answers": ["71", "45", "-30", "70"], "correct": "-30" },
{ "question": "BONUS:What is 36+98?", "answers": ["134", "164", "162", "172"], "correct": "134","isBonus": true },
{ "question": "What is 5x9?", "answers": ["320", "220", "180", "240"], "correct": "220" },
{ "question": "What is 23 + 12?", "answers": ["35", "35", "55", "78"], "correct": "35" },
{ "question": "BONUS:What is 9 * 5?", "answers": ["18", "92", "45", "40"], "correct": "45","isBonus": true },
{ "question": "BONUS:What is 24 / 3?", "answers": ["8", "15", "62", "72"], "correct": "8" ,"isBonus": true},
{ "question": "BONUS:What is 5 * 7?", "answers": ["21", "35", "73", "61"], "correct": "35","isBonus": true },
{ "question": "BONUS:What is 27 / 3?", "answers": ["30", "44", "9", "21"], "correct": "9" ,"isBonus": true},
{ "question": "BONUS:What is 98 + 69?", "answers": ["167", "54", "87", "42"], "correct": "167","isBonus": true },
{ "question": "BONUS:What is 14 + 85?", "answers": ["91", "46", "99", "79"], "correct": "99" ,"isBonus": true},
{ "question": "BONUS:What is 35 / 5?", "answers": ["7", "12", "19", "81"], "correct": "7" ,"isBonus": true},
{ "question": "BONUS:What is 8 * 5?", "answers": ["40", "27", "60", "100"], "correct": "40" ,"isBonus": true},
{ "question": "BONUS:What is 20 - 32?", "answers": ["33", "-12", "-10", "46"], "correct": "-12" ,"isBonus": true},
{ "question": "BONUS:What is 9 * 9?", "answers": ["89", "83", "81", "27"], "correct": "81" ,"isBonus": true},
{ "question": "BONUS:What is 77 + 44?", "answers": ["97", "98", "121", "52"], "correct": "121" ,"isBonus": true},
{ "question": "What is 58 - 78?", "answers": ["58", "-20", "48", "33"], "correct": "-20" },
{ "question": "What is 9 * 6?", "answers": ["54", "77", "59", "35"], "correct": "54" },
{ "question": "What is 84 - 76?", "answers": ["50", "52", "73", "8"], "correct": "8" },
{ "question": "What is 35 / 7?", "answers": ["27", "43", "96", "5"], "correct": "5" },
{ "question": "What is 55 - 78?", "answers": ["73", "51", "43", "-23"], "correct": "-23" },
{ "question": "What is 54 - 50?", "answers": ["78", "47", "4", "51"], "correct": "4" },
{ "question": "What is 25 / 5?", "answers": ["48", "5", "65", "75"], "correct": "5" },
{ "question": "What is 87 + 86?", "answers": ["173", "72", "15", "49"], "correct": "173" },
{ "question": "What is 42 + 93?", "answers": ["52", "14", "71", "135"], "correct": "135" },
{ "question": "What is 8 * 7?", "answers": ["47", "19", "56", "47"], "correct": "56" },
{ "question": "What is 18 / 3?", "answers": ["96", "6", "34", "94"], "correct": "6" },
{ "question": "What is 31 - 25?", "answers": ["99", "6", "35", "17"], "correct": "6" },
{ "question": "What is 8 * 5?", "answers": ["72", "42", "70", "40"], "correct": "40" },
{ "question": "What is 28 / 4?", "answers": ["13", "78", "62", "7"], "correct": "7" },
{ "question": "What is 19 - 95?", "answers": ["51", "61", "-76", "15"], "correct": "-76" },
{ "question": "What is 22 - 79?", "answers": ["39", "-57", "97", "27"], "correct": "-57" },
{ "question": "What is 8 * 6?", "answers": ["13", "20", "48", "13"], "correct": "48" },
{ "question": "What is 33 + 48?", "answers": ["38", "81", "55", "33"], "correct": "81" },
{ "question": "What is 24 + 79?", "answers": ["89", "97", "17", "103"], "correct": "103" },
{ "question": "What is 32 - 72?", "answers": ["97", "66", "25", "-40"], "correct": "-40" },
{ "question": "What is 52 - 64?", "answers": ["74", "-12", "46", "74"], "correct": "-12" },
{ "question": "What is 72 / 8?", "answers": ["82", "9", "43", "35"], "correct": "9" },
{ "question": "What is 22 - 95?", "answers": ["82", "46", "15", "-73"], "correct": "-73" },
{ "question": "What is 24 / 3?", "answers": ["31", "14", "8", "32"], "correct": "8" },
{ "question": "What is 24 / 4?", "answers": ["72", "17", "6", "71"], "correct": "6" },
{ "question": "What is 94 + 50?", "answers": ["83", "144", "65", "40"], "correct": "144" },
{ "question": "What is 19 - 54?", "answers": ["-35", "67", "35", "60"], "correct": "-35" },
{ "question": "What is 86 - 46?", "answers": ["70", "70", "40", "34"], "correct": "40" },
{ "question": "What is 24 - 85?", "answers": ["56", "-61", "87", "44"], "correct": "-61" },
{ "question": "What is 35 / 7?", "answers": ["27", "5", "94", "94"], "correct": "5" },
{ "question": "What is 72 / 8?", "answers": ["86", "65", "80", "9"], "correct": "9" },
{ "question": "What is 34 + 81?", "answers": ["115", "50", "20", "97"], "correct": "115" },
{ "question": "What is 40 - 70?", "answers": ["71", "45", "-30", "70"], "correct": "-30" }
]